imleagues.com 2013-05-30

# IMLeagues Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**  
**How we keep your information safe: Effective January 20, 2008**

**imleagues Principles:**  
We built imleagues to make it easy to share information with your students, teammates, coaches, refs, fans, friends and people around you. But we also understand that you may not want everyone in the world to have the information you share on imleagues; that is why we give you control of your information. Our default privacy settings limit the information displayed in your profile to your networks and other reasonable community limitations that we tell you about.

Imleagues follows two core principles in personal information handling practices:

**1\. Control over your personal information:** imleagues helps you share information with your friends and people around you. You choose what information you put in your profile, including contact and personal information, pictures, interests and groups you join.

**2\. Access to the information others want to share:** There is an increasing amount of information available out there, and you may want to know what relates to you, your friends, and people around you. We want to help you easily get that information.

**imleagues's Privacy Policy** :  
imleagues's Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect and use the personal information you decide to share, and help you make informed decisions when using imleagues, located at www.imleagues.com and its directly associated domains (collectively, "imleagues" or "Website")

By using or accessing imleagues, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact our privacy staff at [privacy@imleagues.com](mailto:privacy@imleagues.com).

**Policy Changes:**  
We reserve the right to change this Policy at any time. We may use personal information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in this privacy policy. If our privacy practices change we will post the policy changes to our web site and notify you by indicating the date the privacy policy was last updated. We encourage you to check back at our web site periodically if you are concerned about how your information is used. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

**The Information We Collect:**  
When you visit imleagues you provide us with two types of information: a) personal information such as (name, email address) you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected by us, and b) non-personally identifiable information that is generated when you interact with our Web Site. 

When you use imleagues, you may form relationships, send messages, perform searches and queries, form groups, set up events, and transmit information through various channels. We collect this information so that we can provide you the service to facilitate user interaction in the imleagues network and to offer personalized features. Email addresses are used for the purposes of inviting new friends to join imleagues, to add users to members' friends' networks, and to send notifications related to the service. With the exception of inviting friends, adding friends, and notifications, a user's email address is not shared or displayed to people within a user's personal network. Users' full names are never directly revealed to other members. To facilitate searching and finding friends and acquaintances on the service, imleagues allows users to search for other members using first and last name and email address. When you update information, we usually keep a backup copy of the prior version for a reasonable period of time to enable reversion to the prior version of that information.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information/Cookies:** When you enter imleagues, we collect non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the Web Site. This data is used to manage the Web Site, track usage and improve the Web Site services. This non-personally identifiable information may be shared with third parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser. By default, we use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID (but not your password) to make it easier for you to login when you come back to Imleagues. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set -- each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. However, you must enable cookies for Imleagues in order to use most functions on the site. Please note that Imleagues allows 3rd party advertisers that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer, and that by using Imleagues, you consent to the setting and accessing of such cookies on your computer. Advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this Privacy Policy.

**User Content:** You post User Content (as defined in the imleagues Terms of Use) on the Site at your own risk. Although we allow you to set privacy options that limit access to your pages, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that User Content you post on the Site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other Users have copied or stored your User Content.

**Third Party Advertising:** Ads appearing on this Web Site may be delivered to users by imleagues or one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Imleagues only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Promotions/Sweepstakes:** From time to time, imleagues or a partner, may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake or contest on the Site. Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. We may transfer personal information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply.

**Invitation Service:** imleagues members can invite friends to join the service by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system. Imleagues stores the email addresses that members provide so that the respondents may be added to the friend's list of the member sending the invitations, and also to send reminders of the invitations. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. imleagues stores this information to send this one-time email, to register a friend connection if your invitation is accepted, and to track the success of our referral program. imleagues does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations. Your friend may contact us at [info@imleagues.com](mailto:info@imleagues.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

**Links:** imleagues may, but is not obligated, to contain links to third party sites. imleagues is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our Privacy Policy only governs information collected on the Imleagues Web Site. Imleagues may also collect information about you from other sources, such as newspapers, blogs, instant messaging services, and other users of the imleagues service through the operation of the service (e.g., photo tags) in order to provide you with more useful information and a more personalized experience. By using Imleagues, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the Canada and/or the United States. Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on Imleagues is a violation of the Imleagues Terms of Use and should be reported to [privacy@imleagues.com](mailto:privacy@imleagues.com). 

**Children Under Age 13:** imleagues does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information to or on Imleagues. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [privacy@imleagues.com](mailto:privacy@imleagues.com). 

**Children Between the Ages of 13 and 18:** We recommend that minors over the age of 13 and under the age of 18 ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet. 

**Use of Information Obtained by imleagues:**  
When you register with imleagues, you create your own profile and privacy settings. Your profile information, as well as your name, email and photo, are displayed to people in the networks specified in your privacy settings to enable you to connect with people on Imleagues. We may occasionally use your name and email address to send you notifications regarding new services offered by imleagues that we think you may find valuable. If we do contact you, the email will contain a link that allows you to opt-out of further promotions. 

Profile information is used by Imleagues primarily to be presented back to and edited by you when you access the service and to be presented to others permitted to view that information by your privacy settings. In some cases where your privacy settings permit it (e.g., posting a message), other Imleagues users may be able to supplement your profile.

Profile information you submit to Imleagues will be available to users of imleagues who belong to at least one of the networks you allow to access the information through your privacy settings (e.g., teams, geography, friends of friends). Your name, network names, and profile picture thumbnail will be available in search results across the Imleagues network and those limited pieces of information may be made available to third party search engines. This is primarily so your friends can find you and send a friend request. People who see your name in searches, however, will not be able to access your profile information unless they have a relationship to you (friend, friend of friend, member of your networks, etc.) that allows such access based on your privacy settings.

imleagues will send you service-related announcements from time to time through the general operation of the service. For instance, if a friend sends you a new message, or someone posts on your message board, you may receive an email alerting you to that fact.

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.

imleagues may use information in your profile without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We do this for purposes such as aggregating how many people in a network like a team or sports drink and personalizing advertisements and promotions so that we can provide you Imleagues. We believe this benefits you. You can know more about the world around you and, where there are advertisements, they're more likely to be interesting to you. For example, if you put a favorite movie in your profile, we might serve you an advertisement highlighting a screening of a similar one in your town. But we don't tell the movie company who you are.

We may use information about you that we collect from other sources, including but not limited to newspapers and Internet sources such as blogs, instant messaging services and other users of Imleagues, to supplement your profile. Where such information is used, we generally allow you to specify in your privacy settings that you do not want this to be done or to take other actions that limit the connection of this information to your profile (e.g., removing photo tag links).

**Sharing Your Information with Third Parties:**  
imleagues is about sharing information with others (friends, family, your team, coaches, and other players) while providing you with controls that restrict other third parties from accessing your information. We allow you to choose the information you provide to friends and networks through Imleagues. Our network architecture and your privacy settings allow you to make informed choices about who has access to your information. 

Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, imleagues will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by imleagues, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the our Terms of Use or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service.

**Service Providers:** We may provide information to service providers to help us bring you the services we offer. Specifically, we may use third parties to facilitate our business, such as to host the service at a co-location facility for servers, to send out email updates about Imleagues, to remove repetitive information from our user lists, to process payments for products or services, or to provide search results or links (including sponsored links). In connection with these offerings and business operations, our service providers may have access to your personal information for use for a limited time in connection with these business activities. Where we utilize third parties for the processing of any personal information, we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections limiting the use of that information to the Imleagues-specified purposes.

In conjunction with the use of the Imleagues Development Platform, third parties who agree to abide by the imleagues Development Platform Terms of Service, including restrictions on access, storage and use of such data, may have limited access to your personal information. We have undertaken contractual and technical steps to restrict possible misuse of such information by such third parties, but of course cannot and do not guarantee that all third parties will abide by such agreements. Please report any suspected misuse of information to imleagues at [privacy@imleagues.com](mailto:privacy@imleagues.com) and we will investigate any such claim and take appropriate action against the third party

**Demonstration Accounts:** We occasionally provide demonstration accounts that allow non-users a glimpse into the imleagues world. Such accounts have only limited capabilities and passwords are changed regularly to limit possible misuse.

**Lawful Requests:** We may be required to disclose user information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. We do not reveal information until we have a good faith belief that an information request by law enforcement or private litigants meets applicable legal standards. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the imleagues service or using the imleagues name, or to prevent imminent bodily harm. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies.

**Jointly Offered Services:** We may offer stores or provide services jointly with other companies on imleagues. You can tell when another company is involved in any store or service provided on imleagues, and we may share customer information with that company in connection with your use of that store or service.

**Sale of the Company:** If the ownership of all or substantially all of the imleagues business, or individual business units owned by imleagues LLC., were to change, your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy.

**Third Party Advertising:**  
Advertisements that appear on imleagues are sometimes delivered (or "served") directly to users by third party advertisers. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and "web beacons" (also known as "1x1 gifs") to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. Imleagues does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on Imleagues unless you choose to share it with them. 

This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by imleagues and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

**Changing or Removing Information:**  
imleagues users may modify or remove any of their profile information at any time by logging into their account. Information will be updated immediately. Individuals who wish to deactivate their Imleagues account may do so on the My Account page. Removed information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time but will not be generally available to members of imleagues. 

Where you make use of the communication features of the service to share information with other individuals on imleagues, however, (e.g., posting a message on someones board & smack talk) you generally cannot remove such communications.

**Security:**  
imleagues takes appropriate precautions to protect our users' information. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. Because email and instant messaging are not recognized as secure communications, we request that you not send private information to us by email or instant messaging services. If you have any questions about the security of Imleagues Web Site, please contact us at [privacy@imleagues.com](mailto:privacy@imleagues.com).

**Terms of Use, Notices and Revisions:**  
Your use of imleagues, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our Terms of Use and all of its dispute resolution provisions including arbitration, limitation on damages and choice of law. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use at any time. Non-material changes and clarifications will take effect immediately, and material changes will take effect within 30 days of their posting on this site. If we make changes, we will post them and will indicate at the top of this page the policy's new effective date. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or through notice on our home page. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you should first contact our Privacy Officer at [privacy@imleagues.com](mailto:privacy@imleaguess.com). You may also contact us by mail at 66 Bogart Court Princeton NJ 08540
